{
    "subject": "resource/One_Night_at_McCool's",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of One Night at McCool's is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9594520330429077,
            "question": "Is 'One Night at McCool's' primarily an English-language film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.810768187046051,
            "question": "Would someone who only speaks English be able to understand 'One Night at McCool's'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7679450511932373,
            "question": "What language is spoken in the movie 'One Night at McCool's'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6696487069129944,
            "question": "How does the use of English in 'One Night at McCool's' compare to other films of a similar genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6598303318023682,
            "question": "What impact might a different language have on the storytelling of 'One Night at McCool's'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6441786885261536,
            "question": "Does the language used in 'One Night at McCool's' contribute to its overall theme or setting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5204213261604309,
            "question": "Are there any subtitles available for 'One Night at McCool's'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14453884959220886,
            "question": "What other languages might be spoken in addition to English in the movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14215564727783203,
            "question": "Are there any specific dialects or accents of English used in the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11013142764568329,
            "question": "Could the choice of English as the language influence the audience's perception of the characters?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of One Night at McCool's is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4950_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific dialects or accents of English used in the film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4950_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other languages might be spoken in addition to English in the movie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4950_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any subtitles available for 'One Night at McCool's'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4950_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4950_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the film \"One Night At McCool's\" features actors speaking English, and it opens in UK cinemas. This supports the statement that the language of the film is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}